Word to md conversion using Notepad++

1. Enable Hidden characters

2. Global find and replace numeric headers to Bold, e.g.

a- Add '**  ' to end of line as well we remove the Tab from the start of next paragraph, i.e.
Find: \r\n\t
Replace: **\r\n

b- Add ** to start of line:
Find: \r\n५
Replace: \r\n**५


3. Add tags for gathas
a) Replace 'double tab' from start of sentence with '>' - for gatha
Find: '\t\t'
Replace: '>'

b) Find '; \r\n'
Replace ';>\r\n'

OR manually for gathalast

4. Add <br> after end of each paragraph, i.e. 
a)
Find: '\r\n\r\n'
Replace: '\r\n\<br>\r\n'

b)
Find: '\r\n\t'
Replace: '\r\n\<br>\r\n'


To do:
Add a test page called md2xmlview.html on root.
Upload the test xml files into testxml folder on root.
Add links on the md2xmlview.html file to each of the xml files, so they can be viewed on the website with full formatting. 
